#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ ariannahuffington (LinkedIn) www.thriveglobal.com (Company) www.facebook.com/ AriannaHuffington (Other) twitter.com/ariannahuff (Other)

#### **Publications**

Third World America: How Our Politicians Are Abandoning The Middle Class and Betraying The American Dream

Thrive: The Third Metric to Redefining Success and Creating a Life of Well-Being, Wisdom, and Wonder

On Becoming Fearless... In Work, Love, and Life

The Sleep Revolution: Transforming Your Life, One Night At A Time

The Fourth Instinct: Call of the Soul

# Arianna Huffington

Founder and CEO at Thrive Global New York

## Summary

Arianna Huffington is the founder and CEO of Thrive Global, the founder of The Huffington Post, and the author of 15 books, including, most recently, Thrive and The Sleep Revolution. In 2005, she launched The Huffington Post, a news and blog site that quickly became one of the most widely-read, linked to, and frequently-cited media brands on the Internet. In 2016, she launched Thrive Global, a leading behavior change tech company with the mission of changing the way we work and live by ending the collective delusion that burnout is the price we must pay for success.

She has been named to Time Magazine's list of the world's 100 most influential people and the Forbes Most Powerful Women list. Originally from Greece, she moved to England when she was 16 and graduated from Cambridge University with an M.A. in economics. At 21, she became president of the famed debating society, the Cambridge Union.

She serves on numerous boards, including Onex and The B Team.

Her last two books, Thrive: The Third Metric to Redefining Success and Creating a Life of Well-Being, Wisdom, and Wonder and The Sleep Revolution: Transforming Your Life, One Night At A Time, both became instant international bestsellers.

## Experience

Thrive Global
Founder and CEO
September 2016 - Present (4 years)

The Huffington Post Media Group President and Editor-in-Chief May 2005 - August 2016 (11 years 4 months)

## Education

Cambridge University

Master of Arts (M.A.), Economics · (1968 - 1972)